One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
Go ahead.
Find it!
Everything is right where I left it!
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
Reuniendo todos nuestros sueños,
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
partimos en busca de aquello que deseamos.
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for
One Piece!
Objetos como una brújula sólo nos retrasan,
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind
llenos de entusiasmo, tomamos el timón.
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide
¡Incluso un polvoriento mapa del tesoro,
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals
no será una leyenda si lo comprobamos!
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real
En tus propias tempestades...
When the world's got you down,
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
...súbete al biorritmo de alguien.
Their biorhythm will carry you through
¡Está bien pensar en ellos!
We're gonna make the most of it
Reuniendo todos nuestros sueños,
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
partimos en busca de aquello que deseamos.
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for
Con una moneda en el bolsillo, dime:
Got some change to my name,
and maybe you wanna be my friend?
¿quieres ser mi amigo?
¡Estamos, estamos en una travesía!
We are, we are on the cruise!
¡Estamos!
WE ARE!
Aparece Sanji
Unidad de cazarrecompensas
Johnny y Yosaku
Restaurante marítimo
Baratie
Teniente del Cuartel General de la Marina
"Fullbody, Puño de Hierro"
Restaurante marítimo
Zeff, dueño y jefe de cocina
Sanji, sous-chef de cocina
Restaurante marítimo
Cocinero Patty
Cuando era pequeño, extendía...
...un mapa del tesoro en mi mente.
Me aseguraba de que ningún
desconocido se me adelantara...
...en alcanzar ese lugar milagroso que buscaba.
Mi verdadero...
...sueño tiene que realizarse.
Si el mundo cambiase algún día,
llévenme con el yo que nunca supo nada...
...y asegúrense de que los recuerdos no se esfumen.